Once you see it, it's too late.
Smile is a horror, mystery film directed by Parker Finn.
After witnessing a bizarre, traumatic incident involving a patient, Dr.
Rose Cotter starts experiencing frightening occurrences that she can't explain.
Rose Cotter, played by Sosie Bacon.
Joel, played by Kyle Gallner.
Trevor, played by Jessie T. Usher.
Dr. Madeline Northcott, played by Robin Weigert.
Laura Weaver, played by Caitlin Stasey.
Dr. Morgan Desai, played by Kal Penn.
Smile is a 2022 American supernatural psychological horror film written and
directed by Parker Finn, in his feature directorial debut.
A follow-up to Finn's short film Laura Hasn't Slept (2020), it stars Sosie Bacon as a therapist who witnesses the bizarre suicide of a patient, then
becomes overwhelmed with increasingly disturbing and daunting visions that lead her to believe she is experiencing something supernatural.
It also features Jessie T.
Usher, Kyle Gallner, Kal Penn, and Rob Morgan, as well as Caitlin
Stasey reprising her role from Laura Hasn't Slept.
A feature adaptation of Finn's short was announced in June
2020, and the cast was added in October 2021.
Principal photography began that month in New Jersey and ended in November.
It was originally set for release on the streaming service Paramount+, but the distributor,
Paramount Pictures, released it theatrically after positive test screenings.
Smile premiered at Fantastic Fest on September 22, 2022, and was
released in the United States on September 30.
It received generally positive reviews and grossed over $217
million worldwide on a budget of $17 million.
A sequel without the involvement of Paramount
Players, Smile 2, was released in 2024.
A third Smile film is currently in development.
The film explores themes of suicide, new jersey, post-traumatic
stress disorder (ptsd), therapist, detective.
The tone is dark and mind_bending.